Inspect
youtube2, how did this share go, it can be seen
that today's low was around
1791 and the high was
832 here and if we come and see the 52 week low, then it can be
seen here that the low was ₹353
and the high was
₹1 here, so it can be seen that there is a good
movement here, if you want, you
can come and do intraday trading here, before that,
if you want to come and trade here, then
I will give you a position, you
can try out, it can be seen that you come and sell
it here,
sell it around at what price
and you can come and maintain the AS here,
its target is going to be around
to 1781, ok, you can get a good profit,
trade carefully and do
not do any work without AS. If you have any doubt, then
you can see below  You can come and ask in the comment section
and if you are not on this channel then
subscribe to this channel and do not forget to press the bell icon
so that you get the first update.
Thank you for watching this video guys,
thank you.